{
    "subject": "resource/Poli\u00e7a",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Poli\u00e7a is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9542498588562012,
            "question": "Is Poli\u00e7a a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990527749061584,
            "question": "Where is Poli\u00e7a from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.760066032409668,
            "question": "Is Poli\u00e7a an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7254281044006348,
            "question": "Poli\u00e7a hails from which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697951555252075,
            "question": "What country is Poli\u00e7a associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.631668746471405,
            "question": "What nationality is Poli\u00e7a?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6196950674057007,
            "question": "Where are Poli\u00e7a's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6167485117912292,
            "question": "In what nation did Poli\u00e7a form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6145948767662048,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Poli\u00e7a?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08801990747451782,
            "question": "Can you name a musical group from the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Poli\u00e7a is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8900_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Poli\u00e7a?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8900_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what nation did Poli\u00e7a form?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8900_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are Poli\u00e7a's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8900_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8900_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can answer your question as follows:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Poli\u00e7a is an American indie electronica band (or American pop band) from Minneapolis, Minnesota. This suggests that the statement \"Poli\u00e7a is from United States\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the fact that multiple documents mention Poli\u00e7a as an American band, confirming their origin in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}